After the war was won, the battle for peace began.
Emperor is a drama, history, war film directed by Peter Webber.
As the Japanese surrender at the end of WWII, Gen.
Fellers is tasked with deciding if Emperor Hirohito
will be hanged as a war criminal.
Influencing his ruling is his quest to find Aya, an
exchange student he met years earlier in the U.S.
General Bonner Fellers, played by Matthew Fox.
General Douglas MacArthur, played by Tommy Lee Jones.
Aya Shimada, played by Eriko Hatsune.
Takahashi, played by Masayoshi Haneda.
Mitsuko Kajima, played by Kaori Momoi.
General Kajima, played by Toshiyuki Nishida.
Emperor is a 2012 American-Japanese historical
drama film directed by Peter Webber.
Tommy Lee Jones and Matthew Fox star in lead roles as General Douglas
MacArthur and Brigadier General Bonner Fellers respectively.
The film explores themes of atomic bomb, emperor, based on
true story, japanese surrender, us military.
The tone is emotional.